A Guide to the Wayne Perkins Collection, 1835-1996
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series IV. Photographs and Postcards, 1887-1987.
  - Subseries B. Postcards, [1906?]-1987.
    - Railroad-related scenery (Box-folder 7-6)
      - Natural Tunnel, Virginia, 1933.
      - Natural Tunnel, Virginia: Virginia and Southwestern Railway line [inkblotter], n.d.
      - Pembroke, Virginia: "view of Virginian Railway while under construction," n.d.
      - Petersburg, Virginia: Norfolk & Western Railway station, 1916.
      - Portsmouth, Ohio: Norfolk & Western Railway terminal, 1912.
      - Princeton, Virginia railway yard, [1909?].
      - Pulaski, Virginia: Pulaski Iron Company furnace, 1916.
      - Radford, Virginia: New River bridge, 1912.
      - Richmond, Virginia: scene at Sixteenth and Dock, showing three track levels, holding trains of the Chesapeake & Ohio, Seaboard, and Southern railways, 1923.
      - Roanoke, Virginia: Norfolk & Western Railway general offices, 1919.
      - Roanoke, Virginia: Norfolk & Western Railway shops, 1912.
      - Roanoke, Virginia: trainyard and cityscape, n.d.
      - Salem, Virginia: passenger station, [1906?].
      - Stoneville, North Carolina: Norfolk & Western Railway station, n.d.
      - Wytheville, Virginia: Fourth Avenue Hotel, n.d.
      - Unidentified scene along the Norfolk & Western Railway, n.d.
    - World War II-era aircraft (Box-folder 7-7)
      - Boeing B-17 "Flying Fortress" bomber, n.d.
      - Boeing B-29 "Superfortress," n.d.
      - Boeing P-26A fighter, n.d.
      - Consolidated B-24D "Liberator," n.d.
      - Curtiss P-6E "Hawk," n.d.
      - Curtiss P-36A "Hawk," n.d.
      - Curtiss P-40N "Warhawk," n.d.
      - Junkers JU-88D-1 "Zerstoerer," n.d.
      - Kawanishi Nik2-J Shiden-Kai "George 21," n.d.
      - Lockheed P-38L "Lightning," n.d.
      - North American B-25B "Mitchell," n.d.
      - Republic P-47N "Thunderbolt," n.d.
      - Supermarine "Spitfire" Mark XVI, n.d.
    - Southwestern United States scenery, n.d. (Box-folder 7-7)
      [9 items]
- Oversize Materials, 1874-[1928?].
  - "The Atlantic Coast Line of Railways to the South" map, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Baltimore & Ohio Railroad Washington D.C. excursion broadside, 1891. (Folder 1)
  - "Map of the Chesapeake & Ohio Railway and Connections," n.d. (Folder 1)
  - "Norfolk and Western Railroad and Connections" map, n.d. (Folder 1)
  - "Norfolk and Western is Backbone of City's Prosperity" - Roanoke Times, 1926. (Folder 1)
    [photostatic copy]
  - Ohio Southern Railroad timetable, 1900. (Folder 1)
  - "Map of the Richmond and Danville R. R. System and Connections," n.d. (Box 8)
  - Roanoke Machine Works equipment trust bonds, 1888. (Box 8)
  - Union Station (Bristol, Tennessee/Virginia) railway time card, 1905. (Folder 1)
  - "Map of the Virginia, Kentucky and Ohio Railroad," 1881. (Folder 1)
  - "Westinghouse Automatic Air Brake as Applied to a Locomotive" schematic, n.d. (Box 8)
  - "The Westinghouse Automatic Brake" schematic, n.d. (Folder 1)
  - "Railroad Map of Virginia" by Jed. Hotchkiss, 1874. (Folder 1)
  - "South West-Virginia Mineral Resources & Railway Facilities" map, 1883. (Folder 1)
  - Photographs
    - Norfolk & Western Railway 14 and 37 wreck at Rural Retreat, Virginia, 1920. (Folder 1)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway 549, n.d. (Box 8)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway "West Yard wreck," [1928?]. (Folder 1)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway employees in company dining room, n.d. (Box 8)
    - "Clarkside, Northfork, West Virginia," n.d. (Folder 1)
    - Ice-clogged river at train trestle (identified as New River, possibly near Byllsby Dam, Virginia), n.d. (Box 8)
      [photograph by Bryant of Cliffview, Virginia]